（マコ）ん〜
（蟇郡(がまごおり)）ま… 満艦飾(まんかんしょく)！
Mankanshoku?
Hey!
（蛇崩(じゃくずれ)）
ちょっと！ なんで劣等生が
極(ごく)制服着てるの？
Why's the underachiever
wearing an Ultima Uniform?
What's the meaning of this, Iori?
（猿投山(さなげやま)）
どういうことだ 伊織(いおり)！
Right now, our top priority is
to increase our combat potential.
（伊織）今は こちらの戦力を
増やすのが先決だ
Mankanshoku showed the greatest increase
in parameters compared to her base state.
極制服を着たときと
着ないときとの戦闘力の差が—
いちばん大きかったのが
満艦飾君だったわけだね
It was the most logical conclusion.
（犬牟田(いぬむた)）極めて論理的な結論だ
Iori, I think you set a new
personal speed record on that one.
（犬牟田）
伊織 最速縫製記録更新だな
Yeah. This will be the last set
of Ultima Uniforms I ever make,
（伊織）ああ
最後の極制服だからな
so I'm going to give it everything I have!
全部の引き出しを
空にするつもりさ！
Anyway, we're busy. Talk to you later.
（通信機:犬牟田）
じゃ 忙しいから切るよ
おい！
Hey!
Seven-Hundred-Plus-299-Strong
Super Suction Saver!
（マコ）999連式 急急救命吸引具
SEVEN-HUNDRED-PLUS-299-STRONG
SUPER SUCTION SAVER
Savor this severe savior!
キューキューキューのキュ〜ン！
Hey!
（黄長瀬(きながせ)）おい！
What are you dawdling for?
何をぼやぼやしてる！
Haven't you guys
fought naked all this time?
今までは裸一貫で
戦ってきたお前たちだろ！
And look at you now.
You call yourselves nudists?!
それでも裸のヌーディストか！
（黄長瀬）とうっ！
...I don't think we ever said we were...
（猿投山）
そんな面白いものになったつもりは
さらさらないが…
...but we can't let Mankanshoku fight alone....
（蟇郡）
満艦飾１人に任せてはおけんな
Let's go.
（蛇崩）いきますか
う〜りゃ〜！
Eat this!
（蛇崩･猿投山）トォ〜！
IN HEAVEN'S STEAD,
WE SMITE CLOTHING
Don't you get full of yourselves now,
（縫(ぬい)）いい気になるなよ！ プッ
Honnouji Academy brats!
本能字(ほんのうじ)学園のゴミどもが！
EPISODE 23
IMITATION GOLD
unmei no ito wo tachikitta sono saki ni
It all begins when we sever the threads of fate
senobi shiteitanda
I was trying to be someone I'm not
kutsuzure darake no
In a cramped world
semai sekai de
With no breathing room
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
egao no uragawa
I thought I'd concealed it
kakushita tsumori de
Behind the smile that masked my face
dakedo itsumo kimi ni wa
But it doesn't work on you
minukarete shimatte ite
You always see through my facade
konna no wa hajimete de
Nobody's ever unraveled me like this before
tomadou kedo
I don't know what to do
hoka no dare ni mo kikonasenai
Nobody else can pull these outfits off
nandaka wakannai
A somewhat ambiguous fever
atsusa ga mune wo kogasu kara
Threatens to burn our hearts away
unmei no ito taguriyoseta sono saki ni
It all begins once we rein in the threads of fate
ima atarashii yoake ga kuru
A new day will dawn for us
omoi wa kitto hitotsu
We must be one in spirit
I figured out why Harime Nui
couldn't regenerate her arms.
（通信機:犬牟田）
針目(はりめ)縫の腕が再生できなかった—
理由がわかりました
The Sword Scissor and
Bakuzan can sever Life Fibers,
（犬牟田）片太刀バサミや縛斬(ばくざん)は
生命戦維(せんい)を切断することは可能です
but the powerful kind begin regenerating
immediately after they're cut.
しかし強靱(きょうじん)な生命戦維の場合
切られた直後から再生を開始する
However, cutting them from
both sides at the same time
だが ここで両側から
同時に切れば—
再生しかけた生命戦維を
もう一度 切断できる
lets you sever the regenerating
Life Fibers in succession.
This is the true power of
Dr. Matoi's Sword Scissors.
これが纏(まとい)博士が作った
断ち斬りバサミの本当の力です
SWORD
SCISSORS
Hang on.
（流子(りゅうこ)）待てよ
じゃあ２本の縛斬なら…
...That means twin Bakuzans can...
...have the same effect, yes....
（犬牟田）同様の効果が見込めます
Thank Ragyou for
breaking Bakuzan in half.
縛斬をたたき折った羅暁(らぎょう)に
感謝ですね
（皐月(さつき)）いや
No.
You're the ones who deserve the
gratitude for turning it into two blades.
感謝するのは それを２本の刀に
仕上げたお前たちだ
Oh my.
（犬牟田）
おやおや いつから褒めて伸ばす
タイプになったんですか？
Since when did you get into the
whole positive reinforcement thing?
Ryuuko.
（鮮血(せんけつ)）流子
Yeah.
ああ 見えた！
I see it!
Detecting a high-energy response
from the original Life Fiber's core.
（犬牟田）原初(げんしょ)生命戦維の中央に
高エネルギー反応がありますね
That must be where it's holding all the
people it took captive for their energy.
（皐月）多くの人間を取り込んで
エネルギーとしている部分だ
We can stop it in its tracks
if we take out that part.
そこを狙えば
あいつの機能は停止する
（流子）が あの女も
待ち構えてるってわけだ
But she'll be lying in wait for us, huh?
Ragyou!
羅暁！ てめえよくも
着たくもねえ服
How dare you force me into
an outfit I didn't want to wear!
無理やり着せやがったな
Now it's my turn!
今度は私が身ぐるみ全部
ひっぺがしてやるぜ！
I'm gonna strip you of everything!
Dear me.
That's not how a
seventeen-year-old girl should be talking.
17歳の乙女の言葉遣いではないな
What?
何？
I should reforge you two
from the ground up.
お前たち２人
型紙から取り直してあげよう
...Is that...
それは？
This sword is an ultra-hard Life Fiber.
（羅暁）この剣は超硬化生命戦維
断ち斬りバサミも縛斬も
これをもとに生まれたものだ
It served as the basis for both
the Sword Scissors and Bakuzan.
The original Life Fiber
is everything in one.
この原初生命戦維こそが全て
始まりも終わりも この中にある
The beginning and the end
both reside within it.
（皐月）だあっ
（羅暁）ぬうっ
I will not let you place your
dirty feet upon this sacred being.
（羅暁）この聖なるものの上に
土足で立つことは許さない
Let me show you what one can do
when they surrender themselves to clothing.
素直に服に身を委ねれば
こういうこともできる
Blade Gale!
疾風閃刃(せんじん)！
（皐月）旋風…
Whirlwind Edge!
斬奸(ざんかん)！
（流子･皐月）うおお〜！
（羅暁）ウ〜フフッ フハハッ
She was never gonna go
down without a fight, huh?
ぐっ さすがに手ごわいな
But we can't fall here!
だが 我々が
倒れるわけにはいかない
（流子）
だったら直接あのでかいのを！
Then we should head
straight for that fatass!
（羅暁）フハハハ… バカが！
Fool.
Ryuuko!
流子！
I bet the rest of you are planning to
destroy the transmitter at Honnouji Academy,
（羅暁）残りの連中で—
本能字学園の発信装置を
たたくつもりだろうが—
...but let me tell you...
そう甘くはないぞ！
It won't be that easy!
（好代(すくよ)）はいよ マコ！
Here, Mako.
Thanks, Mom!
（マコ）ありがとう お母ちゃん
よ〜し コロッケパワー
エネルギー充填(じゅうてん)完了！
All right!
Croquette power: all charged up!
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
ON A FULL STOMACH
HEAD-ON BATTLE!
Is she eating while fighting?
（黄長瀬）
戦いながら食ってるのか！
（又郎(またろう)）
ウチのコロッケは効くからね〜
Our croquettes can be
super effective, you know.
（ガッツ）ガッツガッツ〜！
Guts, guts!
Now bring it on!
ほ〜ら バッチ来〜い！
Stand back!
下がってろ！
（美木杉(みきすぎ)）うっ どうした？
What's going on?!
It's headed this way.
こっちに向かってる？
It changed directions?
（皐月）方向を変えた？
Don't tell me it wants to
swallow the Naked Sun whole!
まさか 太陽丸ごと
食らうつもりか？
Is it still not done consuming humans?
まだ人間を食い足りないのか
...Like I've been saying...
（羅暁）だから—
Try as you might,
言っているだろう
you can't stop us!
我々を止めることは—
できない
くっ ヌーディストカノン発射！
Fire the Nudist Cannons!
（黄長瀬）衛生兵！
Medics!
BACK-ALLEY
MEDIC
MANKANSHOKU
Right away!
（薔薇蔵(ばらぞう)）おう！
まっかせろ それそれ〜
Leave it to us! There!
（又郎）出来た〜
All done!
That's too many bandages, dear.
Mako can't move now.
（好代）
父ちゃん 包帯巻きすぎて
マコ動けないよ
Oh my God!
（薔薇蔵）何てこった
（又郎）姉ちゃん大丈夫か？
You okay, Sis?
（マコ）私は大丈夫だよ〜
I'm fine.
（薔薇蔵）とてもそうは見えない
You sure don't look it.
There are too many of them.
こいつは多すぎるぜ
But we still have to fight!
（マコ）でも やらなきゃ…
（マコ）う… うう…
（黄長瀬）それ以上は無理だ！
You can't keep going!
But I can't fall here!
でも ここで倒れるわけには
いかないもん！
I have to keep this ship safe!
この船 守らないと
...Ryuuko said...
流子ちゃん言ってた
“この船は—”
that this ship was her whole world!
“魂のふるさとだ”って！
She said nothing of the sort!
（黄長瀬）そんなこと
ヤツはひと言も言ってないぞ！
The Ryuuko in my heart said so!
（マコ）
私の心の流子ちゃんが言ってるの！
Mako.
（流子）
マコ〜 アハハ…
何かあるよ ハハハ…
（マコ）
今だって川の向こうで流子ちゃんが
おいでおいでしてるんだもん
Even now, she's beckoning
to me from across the river!
（流子）
マコ〜 アハハ…
何かあるよ ハハハ…
（黄長瀬）お前 いろいろヤバいぞ
Uh, I think you're in grave peril.
Your opinion is invalid!
（マコ）ご意見無用！
どあ〜！
無理するな 満艦飾
Don't push yourself, Mankanshoku.
For an underachiever,
you sure did well.
劣等生にしちゃ頑張ったじゃない
But it's our job to take it from here.
（猿投山）
だが ここからは俺たちの仕事だ
Now, then.
さて 伊織の最後の極制服
お披露目と参りましょうか
Shall we debut Iori's
last ever Ultima Uniforms?
（四天王）三つ星極制服 最終形態
Three-Star Ultima Uniforms:
Final Form!
Blade Regalia:
（猿投山）剣(つるぎ)の装 奥義(おうぎ)開眼
BLADE
REGALIA
WONDROUS
ENLIGHTENMENT
Wondrous Enlightenment!
Symphony Regalia:
奏(かなで)の装 最終楽章
SYMPHONY
REGALIA
FINAL MOVEMENT
Final Movement!
Probe Regalia:
探(さぐる)の装 真理究明
PROBE
REGALIA
TRUTH DETERMINATION
Truth Determination!
縛(しばり)の装 我心(がしん)開放
Shackle Regalia:
EGO
BURST
SHACKLE
REGALIA
Ego Burst!
The Honnouji Four Devas'
（四天王）
本能字四天王 極戦(きわみのいくさ)装束
Supreme War Regalia!
SUPREME
WAR
REGALIA
Snake!
（蛇崩）蛇！
（犬牟田）犬！
Dog!
（猿投山）猿！
（蟇郡）ガマ！
Monkey!
Toad!
Supreme Smackdown!
SUPREME
SMACKDOWN!
Amazing!
（マコ）すごい すごい！
さすが四天王！
That's our Four Devas!
（黄長瀬）
もったいぶって登場しやがって
Showed up fashionably late, eh?
Sheesh. You girls are so dimwitted.
（羅暁）
まったく物わかりの悪い娘たちだ
いくら逆らおうと—
No matter how much they resist,
humans are meant to submit to Life Fibers.
人類は生命戦維に屈服する
存在にすぎない
Hell no!
（流子）そんなことは ねえ！
The Life Fibers induced the evolution
of this planet's intelligent life.
（羅暁）生命戦維が
この星の知性体の進化を促した
Clothing made beasts
evolve into humans,
服が獣を人に進化させた
人が家畜を育てるようにな
just like how people fatten livestock.
Did you just call us livestock?
（流子）家畜だと
And as people consume livestock,
Life Fibers consume humans.
（羅暁）人が家畜を食すように
生命戦維は人間を食す
As beings that stand
atop Earth's food chain,
この星の生命の連鎖の
頂点にあるものにとって—
they're only doing what's
expected of them, no?
当然の振る舞いではないか
That doesn't mean we should
let them do as they please!
（皐月）だからといって
おとなしく従うわけにはいかない
People have wills of their own!
人間には生きる意志がある
Big words from a pig in human clothing.
（羅暁）服を着た豚が生意気な
That "will" you mention
will soon be gone.
その意志も
すぐに消えるというのに
Your last bastion is almost within reach!
もう 目と鼻の先だぞ
お前たちの最後の牙城が
This is bad, Ryuuko!
The ship's in big trouble!
（鮮血）マズいぞ流子 船が！
わかってる 皐月！
I know.
Satsuki!
うむ！
You think we can't do anything?
（流子）何もできないかどうか—
We'll see about that!
見せてやるぜ！
Finishing Move:
必殺！
Thread Stripper!
戦維喪失！
フン！
（流子）あぐ…
（羅暁）滅びよ
Perish.
流子ちゃ〜ん！
Ryuuko!
流子ちゃん 流子ちゃん
流子ちゃ〜ん！
Ryuuko! Ryuuko!
Curse you,
（皐月）おのれ
Ragyou!
羅暁！
Your resistance is futile.
無駄なあがきだ
It was only with Ryuuko's help,
and her Life Fiber Synchronization,
生命戦維と一体化した
流子がいたからこそ—
多少なりとも私と戦えていたのだ
that you were able to
stand against me at all.
You and that imitation Godrobe
aren't even fit to tie my shoelaces.
まがい物の神衣(かむい)をまとったお前では
足止めにもならぬわ
You sad little bitch.
You should know your place.
（羅暁）
己の器も知らぬ哀れな娘よ
お前にできるのは
妹の孤独を慰めるくらいだ
The only thing you're good for is lending
your lonely little sister a shoulder to cry upon.
On your way to Hell together, that is.
地獄への旅路のな
Sure, I might be an imitation,
確かに私はまがい物かもしれん
but looking down on imitations
can come back to bite you.
だが まがい物を侮ると
痛い目を見るのは貴様だぞ
くだらぬな
今さら お前に何ができる？
Ridiculous.
What can you do
this late in the game?
フッ 今は時間稼ぎ
Right now? I can buy us some time.
I am but a decoy!
私は おとりだ
Blade Gale!
疾風閃刃！
Ryuuko?
（羅暁）流子か？
Back then... Don't tell me
she deflected my blade
（羅暁）
あのとき 私の刃(やいば)をはじき—
and jumped into the ocean
before I cut her in half!
完全に切断される前に
自ら海に落ちたのか？
Exactly.
（皐月）そういうことだ
She'd let you think you killed her,
お前にやられたふりをして
海の中で傷を再生させ—
regenerate her injured
body parts while in the water,
and then take out
the original Life Fiber.
原初生命戦維にとどめを刺す
That was the idea she came up with.
それが流子の考えだった
I hope you regret wasting
precious time boasting to me, the decoy,
おとりの私に
偉そうな能書きを語って—
無為な時間を過ごした己を恨め
Kiryuuin Ragyou!
鬼龍院(きりゅういん)羅暁！
Impertinent wench!
この さかしら顔が〜！
...You...
（羅暁）貴様
この腕は縛斬と同様の強度を持つ
My arm is every bit as hard as Bakuzan.
Know that I, Gamagoori Ira,
am Lady Satsuki's living shield!
蟇郡苛(いら)
鬼龍院皐月の生きた盾と知れ！
Auntie Ragyou,
羅暁おばさま
乃音(ののん)はこんなに成長しましたわ！
just look at how much
li'l Nonon has grown!
（猿投山）きえ〜！
Enhance your Ultima Uniform all you want.
いくら極制服を強化しようと—
A blind man's sword
will never strike me.
目の見えぬ者の剣が私に当たるか？
I have to go all-out against you, Director.
理事長相手に
手抜きはできないんでね
この目は既に開いている！
My eyes have been opened!
That's where the
"enlightenment" comes from!
だからこその奥義開眼
WONDROUS
ENLIGHTENMENT
Here you go, Lady Satsuki!
（犬牟田）皐月様 これを！
BAKUZAN-GAKO
BAKUZAN-KOURYU
Thanks, Inumuta.
ご苦労 犬牟田！
We won't be able to
withstand one more!
もう１回は防げないぞ
（揃(そろい)）さようですか
Really?
（美木杉）
これ以上 脱ぐものはないが
ない袖を振るのもヌーディストだ
I'm out of cards to play, but nudists always
have an ace or two up their non-existent sleeves.
はあ ごもっともです
I-It is as you say.
Batten down the hatches!
（スピーカー:美木杉）
甲板たため！
Hey, what's the big idea?
おい！ 何をやってる？
まさか お前…
...Wait, you can't be...
（スピーカー:美木杉）
その まさかさ
That's exactly right.
I'm going to use the
Naked Sun's final trump card:
裸の太陽丸の最後の切り札
the Great Naked Blade!
グレートマッパダガー！
その刃で あのひょうたんを
真っ裸ってわけか いいね！
So we're using this blade
to strip that gourd down?
Sounds good!
GREAT
NAKED
BLADE
We're here, Ryuuko!
（鮮血）来たぞ 流子
ここがヤツの中心だ！
This is the core!
Let's go.
行くぞ！
Double-Edged Decapitation Mode!
（流子）
弩血盛武滾猛怒(どっちもぶったぎるもーど)
DOUBLE-EDGED
DECAPITATION
MODE
Finishing Move:
必殺 戦維喪失！
Thread Stripper!
だああ〜！
Status report!
損害状況は？
（エンジニア）
第１ 第３タービン大破
Turbines One and Three
are out of commission!
Turbine Two is almost
out of energy as well!
残る第２タービンも
エネルギーの限界です
Damn it.
（美木杉）クソ！
やはり人力だとここまでか
Is this really all humanity can do?
Shit! This thing's too hard!
クッソ こいつ硬すぎるぜ
Ryuuko!
（鮮血）流子！
（流子）それでも やるしかねえ！
マコたちに約束したんだ！
But I've still gotta do this!
I promised Mako!
This ship is Ryuuko's whole world.
（マコ）この船は
流子ちゃんの魂のふるさとだ
That doesn't just go for
...the Ryuuko in my mind...
私の頭の中だけじゃない
頭の外の流子ちゃんも
きっとそう！
I'm sure the Ryuuko outside
feels the same way!
だって いつもいつも—
...I mean, each and every time...
流子ちゃんは私を待っててくれた
she's always been there, waiting for me!
...So this ship...
だから この船は…
Mr. Mikisugi!
（エンジニア）
美木杉さん 再びタービンが
回転を始めました
The turbine's starting to move again!
In fact, it's rotating at incredible speed!
（エンジニア）
いいえ ものすごい勢いで
回転しています
Just you wait, Ryuuko!
（マコ）
流子ちゃん 待っててね！ 今 私
I'll catch up to you now!
追いつくから！
（流子）マコ？ マコなのか？
（マコ）流子ちゃ〜ん！
Mako?
Is that you, Mako?
Ryuuko!
Mako! It's you, right?
（マコ）流子ちゃ〜ん！
（流子）マコ マコなんだな！
Mako!
...Everyone's...
（流子）マコ！
（マコ）みんなも—
Everyone's here with me!
みんなもいるんだよ〜！
（鮮血）流子 感じるぞ
お前の血のたぎりを！
Ryuuko, I can feel your blood boiling!
It sure is!
（流子）ああ やろうぜ鮮血！
（鮮血）おお！
Let's do this, Senketsu!
Sure!
...It can't be...
バカな
...The original Life Fiber couldn't have...
原初生命戦維が こんなことで
You look like you can't
comprehend what just happened.
（流子）
訳がわかんない顔してるな 羅暁
そりゃそうだ
That comes as no surprise.
After all, we are all
utterly incomprehensible!
訳がわかんないのが
私たちだからな！
You looked down on imitations,
but they've proved to be your downfall.
（皐月）
まがい物と侮ったものが貴様を阻む
People do not live
for the sake of clothing!
人は服のために生きるのではない！
Enough of your futile resistance!
悪あがきを…
（スピーカー:縫）
本能字学園のゴミかすども！
Listen up, Honnouji Academy scum!
The show's not over yet!
ま〜だまだ終わんないのよね
このショータイムは
その神衣も
バカみたいな極制服も—
Those Godrobes,
those silly Ultima Uniforms,
and you were all just the opening act.
君たちは ぜ〜んぶ前座
The main event features the amazing
Grand Couturier and the most amazing supermodel
大トリは
最高のグランクチュリエと—
最高のモデルの
最高にシックでエレガントな—
in an amazingly chic
and elegant fashion show!
ファッションショーよ
心しなさい！
Pay close attention!
Sorry to have kept
you waiting, Lady Ragyou.
（縫）羅暁様 お待たせしました
神羅纐纈(しんらこうけつ)
仕立て上がりでございます
Omnisilk Kouketsu is ready.
Well done, Nui.
（羅暁）ご苦労だったな 縫
愚かな娘たちが不作法したようだな
許せよ
It seems my foolish daughters
acted rather inappropriately with you.
Forgive me.
ああ 羅暁様…
Ah, Lady Ragyou!
...Is this...
（縫）これは？
（羅暁）グランクチュリエの
繊細な指の代わりはできぬが
I can't replace the
Grand Couturier's delicate fingers,
but I can make you capable
of fighting some silly humans.
愚かな人間どもと
戦うことくらいはできよう
This planet will soon be
engulfed by Life Fibers,
すぐに この星は
生命戦維で覆われる
so I don't need to
sew clothes anymore.
もう服を縫う必要はありません
This is more than enough.
これで十分
（羅暁）お前の最後の服か
着心地が楽しみだね
Your last ever design, eh?
I can't wait to find out
how it feels to wear.
（皐月）見事だ 伊織
よくこれだけの極制服を復元した
Brilliantly done, Iori.
I'm amazed you managed to
recreate this many outfits.
（伊織）復元ではありません
I didn't just recreate them.
パワーアップさせています
I powered them up!
さすがだな
I'd expect nothing less.
We've brought our latest
and greatest equipment as well.
（黄長瀬）こっちも最終装備だ
We managed to take out
the original Life Fiber,
原初生命戦維の機能は停止させた
だが まだ鬼龍院羅暁は健在だ
but Kiryuuin Ragyou's
still alive and kicking.
And now we're going to barge into
Honnouji Academy, destroy the transmitter,
今から本能字学園に攻め込み
発信装置を破壊
羅暁と針目縫を捕縛する
and capture both
Ragyou and Harime Nui!
...Soroi...
（皐月）揃
Hot!
あっちっち！
Your eyes are open now, but your
tongue still can't handle the heat, huh?
（蛇崩）
目が開いたのに まだ猫舌なんだ
（猿投山）う… うるさい！
Oh, shut up!
（皐月）カップは割るな
Don't smash the cups.
We're not going off to die.
我々は死にに行くのではない
We're all coming back alive
生きて戻ってもう一度—
to drink Soroi's tea again.
このお茶を飲む
Isn't that right, Soroi?
そうだな？ 揃
お湯はたっぷり沸かしておきます
I'll have the water
ready and boiled for you.
You don't need to come
if you don't want to, you know.
お前が無理に行くことはないんだぞ
I've come too far for that.
（マコ）
ここまできたら そうはいかないよ
...Sis...
（又郎）姉ちゃん
（ガッツ）ガッツガッツ〜
Guts, guts!
（薔薇蔵）心配するな
お前にもしものことがあったら—
Don't you worry.
If anything should happen to you,
鬼龍院財閥から
見舞金 がっぽり取ってやるからな
I'll have the Kiryuuin Conglomerate
compensate us heavily.
（好代）死なない程度に頑張ってね
Give it your all, but not your life.
Here you go. Croquettes.
はい コロッケ
家族の思い 無駄にするなよ
Don't let your family's love go to waste.
私たち呪われた一族の分まで
幸せになれ
Live a life happy enough
for the three of us.
それなら大丈夫だ 皐月
You don't have to
worry about that, Satsuki.
This is the most incomprehensible
family in the entire world.
この一家の訳のわからなさは
地上最強だ
'Kay!
Mako's in your hands.
マコのことは任せます
If anything goes wrong,
I'll wring every last penny out of you.
何かあったときは
鬼龍院財閥が潰れるまで—
搾り上げますから よろしく
Got it?
I'll keep that in mind.
心しておこう
All right, then!
（マコ）よ〜し いくよ！
流子ちゃん 皐月様！
Let's go, Ryuuko, Lady Satsuki!
Yeah.
Life Fiber Synchronize:
Life Fiber Override:
（流子）人衣(じんい)一体
（皐月）人衣圧倒
Godrobe Senketsu!
Godrobe Junketsu!
（流子）神衣鮮血！
（皐月）神衣純潔！
GODROBE
SENKETSU
GOD
ROBE
JUNKETSU
It's time.
よし 取り戻すぞ
我々の学園を！
...We're going to take...
our academy back!
Yeah!
（一同）お〜！
（ガッツ）ガッツ！
Guts!
dareka no sei ni shitara
I always took the easy way out
itsumo kantan dattanda
By pinning the blame on someone else
demo kitto sore ja zutto asu wa yattekonai
But a new day will never dawn on me that way
tabun tada no namakemono deshita
I was probably just really lazy
gomen ne
Sorry
Welcome to the runway of death,
死のランウェイにようこそ
Ryuuko.
流子ちゃん
（羅暁）
この星は生命戦維のもの
This planet belongs to the Life Fibers.
お前たちに天種繭星(あまつだねのまゆぼし) 降誕を
止めることはできない
You people cannot stop the genesis
of the Celestial Seed Cocoon Planet.
CELESTIAL SEED
COCOON PLANET
We will stop it!
（皐月）止めてみせる
鬼龍院の血を引く
我々ならばこそ
As Kiryuuin blood
courses through our veins,
その宿命を覆す
it falls to us to overcome that destiny!
We already put the original
Life Fiber six feet under,
（流子）
原初生命戦維の
息の根は止めた
so quit trying to fight back.
悪あがきはやめろ
Be careful, Ryuuko.
（鮮血）気を付けろよ流子
こいつはヤバいぞ
She's bad news.
今までとは格が違う
This is on a whole different level
to what you've faced up to now.
There's nothing to be
afraid of, Senketsu.
ビビんな 鮮血
神衣は正直だな
Godrobes are so honest.
Behold!
見るがいい 人衣君臨
Life Fiber Subjugate:
Omnisilk Kouketsu!
神羅纐纈(しんらこうけつ)
OMNISILK
KOUKETSU
Time for the finishing touches, Hououmaru.
（縫）
最後の仕上げよ 鳳凰丸(ほうおうまる)
Okay.
（鳳凰丸）はい
You shall know true fear,
真の恐怖を知れ！
my foolish girls!
愚かなる娘たちよ
MANKIND FACES ITS GREATEST CRISIS
（鮮血）
人類最大のピンチに
ＴＲＩＧＧＥＲ(トリガー)も—
As mankind faces its
greatest crisis, so does TRIGGER!
SO DOES TRIGGER
FACE THEIR GREATEST CRISIS
最大のピンチを
迎えようとしていた
FATEFUL SHOWDOWN
Whether the fateful showdown between
mother and daughters will see its conclusion
宿命の親子の戦いが
決着つくかどうかも—
BETWEEN
MOTHER AND DAUGHTERS
SEE ITS CONCLUSION
UP TO
is all up to the staff's hard work!
スタッフの頑張り次第
STAFF
HARD WORK
FIGHT ON
戦えＴＲＩＧＧＥＲ
負けるなＴＲＩＧＧＥＲ
Fight on, TRIGGER!
Pull through, TRIGGER!
TRIGGER
PULL THROUGH
KILL LA KILL
Next week, the KILL la KILL finale:
"Beyond the Infinite Darkness"!
キルラキル 最終回
「果てしなき闇の彼方に」
FINALE
EPISODE 24
BEYOND THE
INFINITE DARKNESS